http://www.wmkeck.org/privacy-policy

W. M. Keck Foundation
HomeAboutFounderHistoryGovernanceAnnual ReportsGrant AbstractsResearchSouthern CaliforniaGrant ProgramsOverviewResearchEligibility and PrioritiesApplication ProcessPhase I: ApplicationPhase II: ProposalGrant AbstractsMedical Research - 2020Science and Engineering - 2020Medical Research - 2019Science and Engineering - 2019Medical Research - 2018Science and Engineering - 2018Medical Research - 2017Science and Engineering - 2017Southern CaliforniaGrant Abstracts2020201920182017Application ProcessPhase I: ApplicationPhase II: ProposalEligible InstitutionsSpecial ProjectsFrequently Asked QuestionsGrantee ResponsibilitiesImpactFor GranteesGrantee PortalGrant ReportsContingent AwardsWhen to ContactGrantee ResponsibilitiesContactStaff Directory
You are here: Home
> Privacy Policy
In This Section:
Privacy Policy
The W. M. Keck Foundation is committed to protecting the privacy of our website visitors.
We do not collect personal information, such as your name, mailing address, or email address, unless you knowingly provide it to us.
By using the W. M. Keck Foundation website or communicating with us by email, you agree to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy.
We use the information that you provide or that may be derived from web tracking only in connection with our internal purposes.
When necessary, we may share information with our service providers and others only for purposes relating to the information’s submission or our mission or operations.
The W. M. Keck Foundation may use cookie technology to analyze site traffic and use.
This information is used solely to assist us in improving our website design and function.
The W. M. Keck Foundation does not otherwise use cookies or other means to collect personal information.
You may elect to block cookies from this site through use of your browser settings.
We never provide or sell any data for private or commercial purposes.
We may ask for the mailing address, telephone number or email address for certain individuals within an organization.
This may include contact information for presidents, chief executive officers, and development officers.
This information is used solely to obtain feedback, provide requested information and to ensure our records remain current.
If you would like to review, update, change or delete information that we have collected from you, please send an email to This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
Please note that changes may not be effective immediately.
Because the W. M. Keck Foundation website contains links to other sites, there is a possibility that those sites may use cookies to collect a visitor’s personal information.
We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other sites.
This privacy statement applies only to this website.
Please visit this page periodically to check our current policy.
Effective Date: 2007
W. M. Keck Foundation © 2020. All Rights Reserved.
ContactSitemapPrivacy PolicySite by Formative
Site design: <a href="http://www.formativegroup.com/">Formative Inc.</a>
